<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>

	</ui:style>
	<g:VerticalPanel>
	<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="teamPanel">
<p>The 2011 Rugby World Cup brings together the top 20 rugby nations in the world to compete for the Web Ellis Trophy. Only two countries have ever won the tournament twice (Australia and South Africa), while for some proud rugby nations the trophy sill eludes their grasp.</p> 

<p>This year the hosts, New Zealand, will feel the pressure of their rugby-mad nation as they seek to win the trophy for the first time since the inaugural tournament in 1987. Meanwhile the holders, South Africa, will have other plans, as will the 2003 winners England, and the powerful French side, who have yet to taste Rugby World Cup success.</p> 

<p>But any nation's plans for World Cup glory can be ruined in the blink of an eye. The tournament has a history of producing upsets, and sending some of the top teams home early with their tales between their legs, so even the minnows can change the course of events. </p>

<p>Browse through the teams on the left to learn more about each country's history at the tournament, and their prospects this year.</p> 
	</g:HTMLPanel>
	<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="positionPanel">
<p>Rugby's appeal comes from its combination of power and speed, and the diverse set skills required to produce a winning team. Each player has a specialist role, but at the same time they all need to be able to perform the key skills of the game: run, catch, pass, tackle and make good decisions.</p> 

<p>To gain a better understanding of the positions, and who are some of the top names in each area, browse through the position listings on the left.</p> 
	</g:HTMLPanel>
	<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="matchPanel">
<p>The winner of the 2011 Rugby World Cup will be decided through a series of 48 Pool and Knockout matches, played over the course of 6 weeks in stadiums all over New Zealand. The excitement culminates on October 23rd, when the two remaining teams meet in Eden Park, Auckland for the final.</p> 

<p>To preview all the matches, browse the list on the left, from Pool stage mismatches, to the final game itself.</p>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</g:VerticalPanel>	
</ui:UiBinder> 